freshmenu.com 2019-04-30

# Fresh food online. Order Tasty food from FreshMenu.

##### Log in to get

### Select dishes at  
₹99 onward

#### Only for new users

__   Use Email

Don't have an account? Sign up

Looks like you don't have an account with us yet. Please signup below. 

OR USE EMAIL

* * *

Already have an account? Log in 

Looks like an account exists with this email/phone number. Please login with existing account to continue. 

Login or signup to get a corporate credit of ₹{{corpCompanyPerUserLimit}} per day 

There has been an issues with your authentication please try again.

OR USE EMAIL

Please use your swissre email.

Please enter a valid email address.

{{forms.login.errors.data.message}}

Please enter a valid password. 4 characters min.

* * *

Don't have an account? Sign up

#### Type in your registered phone number or email ID and we’ll send you an OTP to reset your password.

{{forms.forgotPassword.errors.data.message}}

####  We have sent a verification code to {{ forms.forgotPassword.user.userData }}{{ hasOnlyDigits(forms.forgotPassword.user.userData) ? ' via SMS' : ''}}. Please enter it below. 

{{forms.forgotPassword.OTPerrors}}

{{forms.forgotPassword.errors.data.message}}

Resend code in 00:{{fmResendOtpTimerLimit < 10 ? '0'+fmResendOtpTimerLimit : fmResendOtpTimerLimit}} 

Didn’t receive code? 

Resend Code

####  Create a new password! You’ll be logged in once you’re done. 

{{forms.resetPassword.errors.message}}

Skip and Login 

#### Mobile verification

{{!!forms.mobileVerification.errorMessage ? forms.mobileVerification.errorMessage : "Please enter 10 digit mobile number."}}

Please enter your mobile number, so that we can send you the authentication code.

#### OTP Verification

{{forms.mobileVerification.errors.data.message}}

Please enter a valid OTP.

Enter your OTP code sent to your mobile.

Invalid OTP, please try again.

Didn’t receive SMS?  Resend OTP 

OTP resent. Please check. 

OTP resend failed. Please try again. 

#### Transaction failed

The transaction failed with the payment mode you chose. {{ (cart.corporateDiscount || (cart.apa && cart.apa.length && cart.apa[0].price)) ? 'You can try an alternative payment method.' : 'You could choose to pay with cash or try another mode of payment.' }} 

{{initiatePaymentFailedMsg || "Some of the items availability or price is changed. We do regret for the inconvenience caused."}} 

#### {{fmPaymentFailureErrorMessage}}

Since there are both deliver now and pre-order items in your cart, both will be delivered between {{fmDeliveryEstimate}}. 

To receive the order now, click on "Deliver now" button below ( **Note** : Pre-order items will be removed from the cart) 

×

#### VIEW MENU FOR

×

## Choose Location

Current location is not serviceable.

×

## Add New Address

{{addressError.message}} 

Refund and Privacy Policy 

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

**This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology  Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the**  **Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated**   **by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital**   **signatures.**

For the purpose of these Privacy policies, wherever the context so requires  **"You"**  or  **"User"**  shall mean any natural or legal person who visits our platform, either just for the purpose of browsing [www.freshmenu.com](http://www.freshmenu.com/) (our “ **Website** ”) website or the **Freshmenu app** to buy our product. The term  **"We"** ,  **"Us"** ,  **"Our"**  shall mean Foodvista India Private Limited.

**_Definitions_**

“ **App(s)** ” shall mean applications for mobile and includes Freshmenu App.

“ **Device(s)** ” shall mean a desktop computer, laptop computer, tablet, mobile phone, smart watch or such other electronic equipment.

“ **Force Majeure Event** ” shall mean any event that is beyond our reasonable control and shall include, without limitation, sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action or any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorized access to your mobile or storage device, crashes, breach of security and encryption.

“ **Personal Information** ” refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person, to whom such information pertains including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number and email address disclosed by you in relation to the services available on the Platform.

“ **Sensitive personal data or information** ” consists of information relating to the following:

  1. passwords;

  2. financial information such as bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details;

  3. physical, physiological and mental health condition;

  4. sexual orientation;

  5. medical records and history;

  6. Biometric information;

  7. any detail relating to the above clauses as provided to body corporate for providing service; and

  8. any of the information received under above clauses by body corporate for processing, stored or processed under lawful contract or otherwise.

**“Third Party** ” refers to any person or entity other than you or us.

## SECTION 1 – WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT

**Personal Data** **:  **We collect personal data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us to place order for our products or to inquire about any information, respond to one of our surveys. 

**Personal Information provided by you in relation to the use of the Platform:  **In order for us to enable successful delivery of your order to you, we collect your Personal Information as may be required for the purposes connected thereto when you place an order on the Platform.

We may be required to disclose such Personal Information to the Third Parties solely in connection with purchase, sale and delivery of your order in accordance with the terms and conditions stipulated by such Third Party.

We use the details provided by you during check out to ensure that orders are successfully delivered on time, and to keep you informed on the status of your order.

**Personal Information provided by you in relation to the registration process:** In order to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience and in order to take advantage of certain features available on the Platform including, but not limited to, public forums, accessing or uploading reviews or taking part in surveys, you will be asked to complete an online registration form which will provide us with Personal Information. In the event you register with us, you will also be asked to choose a user identity and password in order to identify yourself during future uses of the Platform.

You can also register on the Platform by logging into online accounts you may have with Third Party social networking sites (“ **SNS** ”) (e.g. Facebook, Twitter); each such account, a “ **Third Party Account** ”, via our Platform as described below. As part of the functionality of the Platform, you may link your account with Third Party Accounts, by either: (i) providing your Third Party Account login information to us through the Platform; or (ii) allowing us to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account. You represent that you are entitled to disclose your Third Party Account login information to us and/or grant us access to your Third Party Account (including, but not limited to, for the purposes described herein), without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating us to pay any fees or making us subject to any usage limitations imposed by the applicable SNS. If you decide to register by logging into a Third Party Account via our Platform, we will obtain the Personal Information you have provided to the applicable SNS (such as your “real” name, email address, profile picture, names of SNS friends, names of SNS groups to which you belong, other information you make publicly available via the applicable SNS and/or other information you authorize us to access by authorizing the SNS to provide such information) from your Third Party Accounts and use that information to create your account and profile page and you will become a member. Depending on the Third Party Accounts you choose and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, you understand that by granting us access to the Third Party Accounts, we will access, make available and store (if applicable and as permitted by the SNS and authorized by you) the information in your Third Party Accounts so that it is available on and through your account on the Platform. If there is information about your “friends” or people with whom you are associated in your Third Party Account, the information we obtain about those “friends” or people with whom you are associated, may also depend on the privacy settings such people have with the applicable SNS.

We also collect certain additional information that is not Personal Information which you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your account profile. When you use our Services, we collect information about you in the following general categories.

If you permit the App to access the address book on your Device through the permission system used by your Devise platform, we may access and store names, contact and messages information from your address book to facilitate any form of interactions through our Services and for other purposes specified in this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use.

In connection with facilitating this service, we receive call data, including the date and time of the call or SMS message, the parties’ phone numbers, and the content of the SMS message, etc.

**Collection of Sensitive personal data or information:**  We do not collect, store or process Sensitive personal data or information as part of our services on our Platform.

**Others:**  In addition to the cookies, we may also collect information to enable us to understand you better so that we can improve (i) your user experience; (ii) to assist our customer service and technical support personnel; and (iii) put processes in place to prevent fraud and unlawful use. In an effort to make the Platform effective and improve the Platform, certain information may be collected each time you access the Platform. Such information may be saved in server logs in an encrypted form which may not identify you personally. Such information or data may include, but shall not be limited to, IP address, your server details, duration of your visit, date, time or purpose of your visit. In addition to cookies we use web beacons, ad tags, pixels to advertise as part of the Platform. The abovementioned data may be used by us and may be shared with our sponsors, investors, advertisers, developers, strategic business partners or other associates to enhance and grow the user experience in relation to the Platform.

URLs: In general, You can browse our Website/App without telling Us who You are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once You give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information for the fields that are optional. We may automatically track certain information about You based uponyour behaviour on Our Website/App. We use this information to do internal research on Our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve Our users. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL You next go to (whether this URL is on Our Website or not), your browser information, and your IP address.

**Cookies** : We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Website to help analyse our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits. Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

The cookies used by us are listed as follows for your information to opt-out of cookies or not.

  * _session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Freshmenu to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc)
  * provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits
  * _secure_session_id, unique token, sessional storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.
  * Your payment details
  * Your IP address and
  * Any other personal information which you give us in connection with the Services.
  * Wherever We collect personal data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy. If You send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to You.

**Payment Information:**  If You transact with Us, We collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit / debit card number and a credit / debit card expiration date and/ or other payment instrument details and tracking information from cheques or money orders.

## SECTION 2: WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION

2.1 We use personal information to provide the delivery of Our products to You. To the extent We use your personal information to market to You, We will provide You the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe transaction; collect money; measure consumer interest in Our products, inform You about online and offline offers, products and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect Us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce Our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to You at the time of collection.

2.2 In Our efforts to continually improve Our product offerings, We collect and analyse demographic and profile data about Our Users' activity on Our Website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with Our server, and to administer Our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify You and to gather broad demographic information.

## SECTION 3 – CONSENT

3.1 When You provide Us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, it is deemed that You have consented to the use of your personal information by Us to carry out the transaction as requested.

3.2 In the course of business, if your personal information for any secondary reason, We shall specify the reason for requiring such information. Upon such request, You shall have the option to refrain from revealing such information to Us.

3.3 If after You consent, either impliedly or expressly, for your personal information to be used by Us, You change your mind, You may withdraw your consent for Us to contact You, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time. Such withdrawal of consent shall be communicated to Us either through an email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#4b22252d240b2d392e3823262e253e65282426) or by contacting Us at our at our corporate office.

## SECTION 4 – DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

4.1 We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of Our Website; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to You as a result of such sharing unless You explicitly opt-in.

4.2 We may disclose personal information of You if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our Users or the general public.

## SECTION 5 – FRESHMENU

5.1 All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

5.2 PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by Our store and its service providers.

5.3 For more insight, you may also want to read Freshmenu’s Terms of Service here or Privacy Statement here.

## SECTION 6 \- THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

6.1 We may engage the services of third parties to help us serve Our customers better. In general, the third-party services providers engaged by Us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to Us.

6.2 However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information We are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions and

We recommend that You read their privacy policies so You can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these third party service providers.

6.3 In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

6.4 Once you leave Our website/App or are redirected to a third-party website or application, You are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

6.5 When you click on third party links on Our Website, We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and for the loss or consequential damage that may be caused to you and encourage You to read their privacy statements.

## SECTION 7 – SECURITY

7.1 To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

7.2 If You provide Us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although, no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

## SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT

8.1 By using this site, You represent that You are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

## SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

9.1 We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. If We make material changes to this policy, We will notify You here that it has been updated, so that You are aware of what information We collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, We use and/or disclose it.

9.2 If our Website is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to You.

CONTACT INFORMATION

: For any query, grievance, complaint or any other information that may be required by You, You may contact Our Privacy Compliance Officer at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0a63646c654a6c786f7962676f647f24696567) and We shall ensure that We help resolve the same within a period of 48 (forty eight) hours.
